The last thing we need to do is the lips and then this look is complete.
Again, we're sticking with natural, obviously, so I'm using a very, very neutral lip liner.
It's kind of a nude color.
Very, very neutral.
That's what you want to use.
You don't want to use anything that has too much color, that's going to give too much definition or a line.
You want it to blend completely.
This is a nice creamy lip liner also, so it's going to go on nice and smooth.
What you want to do is you want to line the entire lip.
Just outline your natural lip line.
If you have very small lips, you can go a little over your natural lip line.
Then you want to fill in the whole entire lip.
Just kind of like you're drawing with a crayon.
The whole lip needs to be filled in with this color.
That's going to keep it looking blended.
It's going to keep your lipstick on longer.
It's going to take all the color out in your lips and we're going to create that very neutral lip look.